Guide to the Barbara Guest Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Barbara Guest papers
1923-2006
YCAL MSS 1185
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
71
(171 boxes)
Guest, Barbara, 1920-2006
Conditions Governing Access
The Barbara Guest Papers is open for research.
Boxes 144-152 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 153-154 (born digital material): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from James S. Jaffe on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, the George B. Alvord Fund, the Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, the Sinclair Lewis Fund, and the Ezra Pound Archive Fund, 1993.
Purchased from Granary Books on the Ezra Pound Archive Fund, 1997.
Purchased from James J. Jaffee on the Sinclair Lewis Fund, 2002.
Purchased from James S. Jaffe on the Alfred Z. Baker, Jr. Fund, the Sinclair Lewis Fund, the Thornton Wilder Memorial Fund, 2007.
Purchased from James S. Jaffe on the Elizabeth Wakeman Dwight Memorial Fund, 2008.
Arrangement
Organized into nine series: I. Correspondence, 1940-2006. II. Writings, 1953-2004. III. Personal Papers, 1943-2006. IV. Professional Papers, X. V. Photographs, circa 1923-2004. VI. Artwork, 1953-1995. VII. Printed Material, 1960-2004. VIII. Audiovisual Material, 1963-2000. IX. Born Digital Material, 1983-2006.
Scope and Contents
The Barbara Guest Papers span 1923 to 2006 and document Guest's life as a prominent American poet, her personal and professional relationships with other writers, and her personal life as a wife, mother, and friend. The papers include drafts of writings, correspondence, personal and professional papers, photographs, artwork, printed material, audiovisual material, born digital material, artwork, and a typewriter.
Biographical / Historical
Barbara Guest, American author. Guest was born Barbara Pinson in Wilmington, North Carolina on September 6, 1920. She died on February 15, 2006 in Berkeley, California.
LCSH 150 ‡a Authors, American ‡y 20th century ‡v Archives; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Biographers -- United States -- 20th Century; Born digital; Videocassettes; Video recordings; Audiocassettes; Phonograph records; Sound recordings; Audiovisual materials; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Realia; Guest, Barbara, 1920-2006
- Correspondence, 1940-2006; Series I
  Arrangement
  Organized into two subseries: General correspondence and Other correspondence
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence includes correspondence with friends, family, colleagues, and other individuals, relating to Guest's professional and personal life.
  - General correspondence
    General correspondence subseries contains letters from individuals to Guest. Correspondents notably represented are Johannes Bellharz, Mei-Mei Berssenbrugge, Susan Clark, Robert Dash, Double Day & Company, Anne Dunn, Rachel Blau DuPlessis, Helen Frankenthaler, Kathleen Fraser, and Rena Rosenwasser. Enclosures such as writing drafts and photographs are noted when present.
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent's last name.
    - Abbott, Mary, 1959-10-19-2005-04-14 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
      Includes a photograph of Mary Abbott, 1999
    - Abish, Walter, 1970-12-08-1990-05-16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Includes photocopies of poems by Abish
    - Academy of American Poets, 1964 May 14–2005 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ackroyd, Peter, 1974-05-15-1994-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Adams, Barbara, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Adnan, Etel, 1995-03-07-2003-01-25 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
    - Adonah, David at Brown University Library, 1963 July 11 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
    - Albiach, Anne-Marie, 1993 March 24–1997 September 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Aldan, Daisy, 1959 June 14–1992 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Aldington, Catherine, 1986 April 14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Alexander, Charles, 2001 December 26 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Alkalay-Gut, Karen, 1987 September 20 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Allen, Don, 1959 September 21–2002 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Frank, 1986 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Allen, Tim, 1999 December 23–2000 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - The America Awards, 1996 January 31–1996 February 21 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - American Academy in Rome, 1987 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - American Biographical Institute, 1992 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - American Letters & Commentary, 1994-12-05-1995-12-20 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - American Poetry Review, 1990-03-12-2005-07-01 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Anania, Michael, 1978 September 23–2006 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Anchor Books, 1961 June 1–1962 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Anderson, Beth, 1997 October–2002 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Andrews, Carol, 2003 April 1–2003 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - AnyArt, 1991 June 29–1992 November 15 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Archive for New Poetry, 1988 October 31–1988 November 8 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Ardagh, Edith, 1981 September 17 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Arshile, 1994 December 1–1994 December 10 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Art and Literature, 1964 January 12–1990 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Art Gallery of Windsor, 1987 July 6–1988 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Art Institute of Chicago, 1985 May 10–1985 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Art News, 1955 October 7 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Arts + Architecture, 1984 November 26 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Artscape, 1991 February 19 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Ashbery, John, 1955-07-20-2006-03-10 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Athena Fine Arts Corporation, 1992 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - The Atlantic Review, 1979 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Augustine, Jane, 1980-03-29-1991-08-04 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - AVEC, 1994 September 8 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Aveline, Claude, 1967 January (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Ayres, Ian, 1999 November 25–2005 September 5 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - "A" General (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Balakian, Anna, 1992-02-27-1996-09-13 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Balzer, Liz, 2000 March 20 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Barnes & Noble, 1986 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Barondess, Jeremiah A., 1990 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Barone Gallery, 1961 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Barr-Sharrar, Beryl, 1996 September 30–2006 March 19 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Basic Books, 1964 March 24–1965 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Bay Area Book Reviewers Association, 2003 February 10–2003 April 1 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Bay Area Summer Poetry Marathon, 2004 March 1–2004 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Bazar, Julia, 1996 July 28 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - BC Research, 1979 June 20–1979 October 30 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Bee, Susan, 1997 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Beilharz, Johannes, 2001 July 30–2006 July 27 (Box 4, Folder 60-63)
      Includes photograph of ZKM Museum in Karlsruhe, Germany and corresponding exhibition catalog, 2003; and unidentified photograph of performers, 2006
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1985 September 12–2006 March 20 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Belladonna*, 2004 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Bergan, Brooke, 1992 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Berkeley Art Museum, 2002 September 5 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Berkeley Public Library, 1995 August 12–1995 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Berkson, Bill, 1976 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Berkson, Lynn, 1980 April 8 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Berls, Robert E., 1964 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Bernadette, Miriam, 1978 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Bernstein, Charles, 1979 October 28–2005 December 2 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Berrigan, Ted, 1962-12-16-1967-05-12 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1980-06-22-2006-07-29 (Box 5, Folder 75-78)
      Includes poem drafts by Berssenbrugge
    - Bertha Schaefer Gallery, 1961 March 1 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Best American Poetry, 1995 January 1 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Bibbins, Mark, 2003 December 21–2004 January 25 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Biddle, Katherine, 1962 March 18–1965 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Bierman, Arthur, 2002 August 6–2002 August 16 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Blackburn, Paul, 1959 April 23 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Black Sparrow Press, 1967 April 17–1997 February 21 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Blaine, Nelly, 1957-09-27-1973-05-08 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Blegvad, Chloë, 1980 April 30–1996 December 23 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Blegvad, Peter, 1987 July 7–2003 August 11 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Blue Mesa Review, 1990 June 4–1990 November 26 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Blue Sky, 2003 March 1–2003 April 17 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Boer, Charles, 1992 June 27 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Bong, Gro, 2002 December 21 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Borden, Lizzie, 1967 January 19 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Bosquet, Alain, 1958 September 17–1960 September 14 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Bouché, René, 1954 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Bowery Poetry Club, 2004 July 9–2005 January 13 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Boyle, Kay, 1966 December 8–1983 December 6 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1964 March 22–1992 October 28 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Branch, Jay B., undated (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Brick Magazine, 2006 March 11–2006 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - British Film Institute, 1986 April 7 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Brodey, James, 1963 November 5–1969 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Brooke Alexander Editions, 1991 March 11 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Broome Street Gallery, 1998 January 3 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Brown, Eric, 2003 January 31–2003 December 4 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Brown University, 1991 December 12–2001 February 27 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Bryher, Winifred, 1977 August 9 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1978 April 3–1985 February 8 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Burning Deck, 1963 June 4–2006 January 8 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Buschendorf, Christa, 1998 December 9–1999 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Byron, Charles, 1953 December 20–1954 June 3 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - "B" General (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Caffe Cino, undated (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - California College of Arts and Crafts, 1998 July 28–1998 November 17 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - California State University, Los Angeles, 1979 March 20 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Cambridge Conference of Contemporary Poetry, 1992 November 12 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Cambridge Poetry Festival, 1987 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Cameron, Michael, 1980 April 12–1981 February 6 (Box 7, Folder 118)
      Includes a poem draft "Practising Dying (III) for Barbara Guest"1980 July 28
    - Campbell, Glenna, 2001 December 24 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Campbell-Thiebaud Gallery, 1995 July 11–1996 January 19 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Caples, Garrett, 2002 December 24–2005 February 3 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Carcanet Press, 1992 January 26–2005 December 7 (Box 7, Folder 122)
      Includes catalog
    - Card, Macgregor, 1997 January 5 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Carey, Tom, 1991 April 30 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Carlisle, Olga, 1963 May 24–1971 October 8 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Carré d'Art, 2000 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Carroll, Paul, 1960 December 1 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Carter, Rosalynn and Jimmy, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Castro, Jan, 1979 July 16 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Caws, Mary Ann, 1990 March 8 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Cerio, Laetitia, 1980 June 10 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Chadwick, Whitney, 1987 April 22 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Chatto & Windus, 1986 July 30 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Cheim & Read, 1997 February 4 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Chelsea, 1992 January 7–1994 November 21 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - ChemicalBank, 1988 January 12 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Cheng, Anne Anlin, 2004 July 12 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Chicago Review, 1996 August 6 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Citibank, undated (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - City University of New York, 1990 October 2–1997 December 17 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Claremont Resort, 1995 May 3 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Clark, Jeff, 1999 October 31–2005 February 1 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Clark, Susan, 1999 August 23–2003 June 28 (Box 8, Folder 143-144)
    - C Magazine, 1966 May 5 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Coale, Edward H., 1990 June 1 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Cody's Books, 1997 February 5 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Coffee House Press, 2000 March 28 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Cohen Cormier Group, 2006 February 17 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Cohen, Marc, 1989 October 30 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Cole, Norma, 1995 November 1–2004 November 1 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Cole, Peter, 1992 April 23 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Collins, Harold P., 1983 January 10–1983 December 31 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Coltrane, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Columbia: A Magazine of Poetry and Prose, 1988 April 8 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Columbia College Chicago, 1996 February 21 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Colum, Padraic, 1956 November 3–1964 January 4 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Commentary Magazine, 1953 March 11–1953 April 9 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Congdon, A. Kirby, 1963 March 4–1964 January 22 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Conjunctions Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 160)
      Includes proof of Guest's "Shelley in the Navy-Colored Chair"
    - Conoley, Gillian, 1995 April 19–2005 August 24 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Contemporary Authors, 1983 May 11–1992 October 30 (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Cook, Blanche, 2006 June 24–2006 July 1 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Coolidge, Clark, 1997 September 24 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Cooper, Penny, 2003 November 25–2003 December 1 (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - Cooper, Sandi and John, 2006 March 7 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - Corbett, Bill, 1983-09-08-1999-07-30 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Cornford, Adam, 2000 January 16–2000 February 3 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Corpuz, Veronica, 2002 May 27 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Corso, Gregory, 1958-02-14-1958-04-21 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1990 February 13–1993 November 30 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Courtright, Frederick T., 1995 August 18 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Cox, Suellen, 1984 September 11 (Box 9, Folder 173)
    - Crane, Sylvia E., 1963 August 16 (Box 9, Folder 174)
    - Crawford, Fred, 1984 September 27–1985 May 17 (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Crayon, 1996 July 22 (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Creeley, Robert, 2005 February 28–2005 March 4 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Critical Quarterly, 1961 September 26–1962 January 20 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Crowd Magazine, 2005 January 10–2005 October 3 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Cunningham, Paul, 1977 March 22 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - Currier Gallery of Art, 1985 November 4–1986 March 25 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - CutBank Poetry, 2006 February 13–2006 February 20 (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Cycholl, Garin, 2000 April 24 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    - "C" General (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Dale, Gloria, 1995 August 22 (Box 9, Folder 185)
    - D'Almeida, Virginia, 2006 February 18-21 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Danielson, Elena S., 1996 June 17 (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Danto, Arthur C., 1991 February 18–1997 March 6 (Box 9, Folder 188)
    - Darras, Jacques, 1979 April 23–1979 July 26 (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - Darrow, Sharon, 1998 November 3–2000 February 11 (Box 9, Folder 190)
    - Dash, Robert, 1959 April 20-1981 March 25 (Box 10, Folder 191-193)
    - Davenport, Guy, 1978 May 3–1983 June 13 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Davis, Leslie, 1996 May 4 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Davis, Michael T., 2003 June 20–2003 July 18 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Dean, Lori, 2005 March 27–2005 June 17 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - De la Perriere, Donna, 2002 March 29–2004 May 30 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Delos, Kate, 2000 September 6–2006 March 27 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - De Nagy, Tibor, undated (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - De Niro, Robert, 1960 June 2-1963 May 9 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - Denver Art Museum, 1979 January 15–1979 September 14 (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - De Torres, Cecilia, 2001 August 31 (Box 10, Folder 203)
    - Deutsch, R. H., 1978 August 15 (Box 10, Folder 204)
    - Dickison, Steve, 2003 July 10–2006 July 30 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Dickson, Deborah, 1991 January 30 (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Dickson, Jane, 2003 January 14–2005 November 4 (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Dictionary of Literary Biography, 1998 February 24 (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Dienstfrey, Patricia, 1997 October 31–2006 July 30 (Box 11, Folder 209)
    - Diggory, Terence, 2003 May 12–2006 July 3 (Box 11, Folder 210)
    - Dimic, Moma, 1976 January 26 (Box 11, Folder 211)
    - DiPalma, Ray, 1997 May 15–1997 June 10 (Box 11, Folder 212)
    - Disappearing Pheasant, 1991 October 24–1991 November 18 (Box 11, Folder 213)
    - Diver, Maureen, undated (Box 11, Folder 214)
    - Dixon, Elizabeth, 1997 April 21 (Box 11, Folder 215)
    - Dobson, Silvia, 1980 September 6–1985 June 28 (Box 11, Folder 216)
    - Dorian, Donna, 1991 September 30 (Box 11, Folder 217)
    - Doris, Stacy, 1992 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 218)
    - Double Change, 2002 February 14 (Box 11, Folder 219)
    - Doubleday & Company, 1960-10-31-1986-02-05 (Box 11, Folder 220-221)
    - Doubleday France, 1984 September 25 (Box 11, Folder 222)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1958 February 5–1962 November 23 (Box 11, Folder 223)
    - Dunn, Anne, 1973-10-08-2006-03-21 (Box 11, Folder 224-225)
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau, 1979 October 8–2006 April 2 (Box 12, Folder 226-227)
    - Dyer, Geoffrey, 2002 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - "D" General, undated (Box 12, Folder 229)
    - Eastman, Max, 1959 July 9–1968 December 31 (Box 12, Folder 230)
    - Eastman, Yvette, 1959 August 29 (Box 12, Folder 231)
    - Edwards, Ken, 2003 December 6–2003 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 232)
    - Eisenberg, Elyse, 2004 December 26–2005 January 4 (Box 12, Folder 233)
    - Elliott, Crystal, 2003 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 234)
    - Elliott, Stephanie, 2005 March 3–2006 June 6 (Box 12, Folder 235)
    - Elmslie, Kenward, 1965 October 29-1999 November 18 (Box 12, Folder 236)
    - André Emmerich Gallery, 1961 February 27 (Box 12, Folder 237)
    - Equi, Elaine, 1994 February 12–2002 September 28 (Box 12, Folder 238)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1989 January 2–1989 July 27 (Box 12, Folder 239)
    - Estate of Tony Smith, 1990 October 4 (Box 12, Folder 240)
    - Eugene's, undated (Box 12, Folder 241)
    - Ewing, Barbara, 1995 April 3 (Box 12, Folder 242)
    - Exact Change, 1994 August 23 (Box 12, Folder 243)
    - "E" General, undated (Box 12, Folder 244)
    - Faber and Faber Ltd, 1962 May 3 (Box 12, Folder 245)
    - FAIR/Extra!, 2003 June 19 (Box 12, Folder 246)
    - Fairleigh Dickinson University, undated (Box 12, Folder 247)
    - Fantagraphics Books, 1999 May 6 (Box 12, Folder 248)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1992 November 2–1996 May 2 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - Fattal, Simone, 1995 September 22-2004 January 23 (Box 13, Folder 250)
    - Fearing, Kenneth, 1958 October 19–1960 October 29 (Box 13, Folder 251)
    - Fearnhead, Joy, 1992 January 5 (Box 13, Folder 252)
    - Felter, June, 1987 June 2–2004 March 29 (Box 13, Folder 253)
    - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1966 December 28-2005 December 23 (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - Finch, Edward Ridley, Jr., 1990 December 26 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - Finger, Fiona, 1954 November 18–1956 July 1 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Finletter, Eileen, 2006 February 18 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Fish, Adrian, 2006 February 17 (Box 13, Folder 258)
    - Fisher, Jessica, 2002 January 30–2002 March 25 (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - Fizdale, Robert, 1960 November 10 (Box 13, Folder 260)
    - Floating Bear, undated (Box 13, Folder 261)
    - Fodaski, Liz, 1996 January 29 (Box 13, Folder 262)
    - Folder, 1954 April 8 (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Folder Editions, 1960 September 29 (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1996 March 20–1996 April 2 (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Ford, Hugh, 1981 January 10 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Ford, Mark, 2004 May 27–2006 June 11 (Box 13, Folder 267)
    - Fotofilmcolor, 1967 February 13 (Box 13, Folder 268)
    - Fourcade, Dominique, 1959 July 2–1991 April 24 (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - Fourteen Hills, 1997 August 27–1998 April 23 (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1951 February 19-2003 November 6 (Box 14, Folder 271-272)
    - Franklin Furnace, undated (Box 14, Folder 273)
    - Fraser, Kathleen, 1956 May 7–2006 June 11 (Box 14, Folder 274-277)
      Includes writings by Fraser
    - Freedman, Deborah, 1978–1988 (Box 15, Folder 278)
    - Freeman, Jan, 2004 May 18 (Box 15, Folder 279)
    - Freeman, Mary Lou, 2004 October 20–2005 November 5 (Box 15, Folder 280)
    - Freeman, Susan Stanford, 1981 October 26 (Box 15, Folder 281)
    - Freilicher, Jane, 1995 October 16–2005 January 23 (Box 15, Folder 282)
    - French Express, 2003 May 31–2005 October 3 (Box 15, Folder 283)
    - Friedberg, Anne, 1979 May 3 (Box 15, Folder 284)
    - Friedman, Bob, 1961 December 21 (Box 15, Folder 285)
    - Friedman, Susan, 1967 December 22–1980 April 7 (Box 15, Folder 286)
    - Friends of H. D., 1978 November 6–1980 March 24 (Box 15, Folder 287)
    - Frost, Elisabeth A., 2003 October 28–2006 March 6 (Box 15, Folder 288)
    - Frost, Terry, 1959 February 9–1964 April 16 (Box 15, Folder 289)
    - Frumkin, Gene, 1994 June 10 (Box 15, Folder 290)
    - Fruttarolo, Germana, 1986 January 20–1986 December 30 (Box 15, Folder 291)
    - "F" General (Box 15, Folder 292)
    - Gaiteuley, Jane, 1979 July 28–1979 August 11 (Box 15, Folder 293)
    - Gale/Thomson, 2004 April 21 (Box 15, Folder 294)
    - Gallup, Donald, 1979 December 19–1985 September 6 (Box 15, Folder 295)
    - Gander, Forrest, 1994 September 25 (Box 15, Folder 296)
    - Gevirtz, Susan, 1988 February 3–2003 June 10 (Box 15, Folder 297)
    - Gevirtz, Susan, 2003 June 12–2006 March 7 (Box 16, Folder 298)
    - Giordani, Marianne, 1997 January 21 (Box 16, Folder 299)
    - Girard, Vincent, 1991 February 11 (Box 16, Folder 300)
    - Gizzi, Peter, 1987 June 17-2006 March 7 (Box 16, Folder 301)
    - Gluck, Robert, 1996 April 16–1997 March 6 (Box 16, Folder 302)
    - Going, Dale, 1992 June 25–1993 April 7 (Box 16, Folder 303)
    - Gonzales, Julie, 2006 February 19 (Box 16, Folder 304)
    - Goodman, Denise, 1958 May 18-1964 December 14 (Box 16, Folder 305)
    - Goodnough, Bob, 1964-04-03- (Box 16, Folder 306)
    - Gotham Book Mart Gallery, 1988-10-05- (Box 16, Folder 307)
    - Grady, Panna, 1967 May 14–1968 December 8 (Box 16, Folder 308)
    - Graffi, Milli, 1995 April 15–2002 February 23 (Box 16, Folder 309)
    - Graham, Allan, 2004 April 22–2005 February 14 (Box 16, Folder 310)
    - Graham, Gloria, 2004 April 1 (Box 16, Folder 311)
    - Gramercy Review, 1979 February 5 (Box 16, Folder 312)
    - Granary Books, 2000 January 31–2002 February 4 (Box 16, Folder 313)
    - Gray, Tim, 2005 March 15–2006 February 18 (Box 16, Folder 314)
    - Green Integer, 2001 August 23 (Box 16, Folder 315)
      Includes poem draft by Douglas Messerli "Harp on a Mountain of Glass for Barbara Guest"
    - Green, Paul, 1995 June 20 (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - Gregory, Horace, 1978 April 28–1982 February 17 (Box 16, Folder 317)
    - Grinberg, Miguel, 1964 April 22–1964 April 30 (Box 16, Folder 318)
    - Gritt, Sam, 1997 July 16–1997 October 21 (Box 16, Folder 319)
    - Grosman, Tatyana, 1960 April 10 (Box 16, Folder 320)
    - Grosseteste Review, 1978 August 10-1978 November 5 (Box 16, Folder 321)
    - Grosskurth, Phyllis, 1986 June 5 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - Grove Press, 1958 November 7–1961 December 20 (Box 17, Folder 323)
    - G. Smith and Sons, undated (Box 17, Folder 324)
    - Guenther, Charles, 1976 August 2–1979 November 17 (Box 17, Folder 325)
      Includes photocopy of clipping
    - Guest, Angela, 1949 May 3–1950 March 1 (Box 17, Folder 326)
    - Gufline, Camille, 1997 June 7 (Box 17, Folder 327)
    - Guild Hall of East Hampton, 1984 June 24 (Box 17, Folder 328)